globaledge.co.uk 2008-09-22

# Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of all our customers.  We will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail, and your details will not be passed to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit permission.

### Full policy

We have developed this policy so that you may feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information.

Countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) are required to have a similar standard of protection of personal data. This is not always the case outside that area. We do sometimes transfer data outside the EEA and before doing so take steps to ensure that there is adequate protection, as required by relevant Data Protection legislation.

### Use of Personal Information

You may need to register to access our website and where you do not register personal information about you will not be collected by us.

If you register for our services, any details you provide may be stored for use on future visits, as we do not want you to give us any information more than once. The details you give us may be combined with information about your use of the Imageco website(s) and information from other of our records in order to provide you with online services you request.

### Email addresses

We respect the privacy of personal email accounts and we store your email addresses just as securely as other personal information. We will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail, and your details will not be passed to any organisation outside the Group for marketing purposes without your explicit permission.

However, we may use email in response to enquiries you make about our services or service issues.

### Disclosure of information

We take all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data.

We sometimes use other companies to provide some of our services or to provide services to us. To enable them to do this, we may need to let them process your personal information. Our staff and those working for our agents or contractors have a responsibility to keep your information confidential and are only allowed to use it to offer products and services on our behalf.

### Right of access to your information

If you want to know exactly what personal information Global edge holds on you, you can obtain it. If it transpires that the information held is inaccurate, we will make the necessary amendments and confirm to you that these have been made. Please write to the Data Protection Officer at Global edge.

### How we protect your data

Our general Email enquiry forms are not sent via an encrypted channel and for this reason we ask that you do not include confidential information when using them (such as bank account details).

Messages sent and received via the message service when you are logged into your accounts via our internet banking service are encrypted and therefore secure.

### Use of Cookies

**Cookies** – Your website may work with third parties to research certain usage and activities on our website on our behalf. No personal information about you is shared, however in the course of conducting this research these third parties may place a unique "cookie" on your browser.

A cookie is a small file which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard disc and helps Your website understand and track your use of the site and where it can improve the information and services provided. Your website uses cookies solely to gather information on IP addresses, to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movements on the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to other personally identifiable information and will not be used to deliver targeted marketing messages. For information about blocking the use of cookies, please refer to the instructions/help screen on your Internet browser. Please note that you may not be able to use or access certain parts of the site or online services if you block the use of cookies.

**Changes** \- As a result of improvements we make to our services, amendments to laws or regulation or developments in the technology or processes we use, we may change the information we hold about you and/or the way in which or the purposes for which we process such information. Where we require your consent to such change we will notify you of the change. However, unless you inform us otherwise, we will deem your continued use of products and services to which the change relates to constitute your consent to the relevant change.

**Please help us** \- We wish our service to meet your expectations on all occasions. To do so we need the information we hold about you to be accurate and up to date. Please help us by informing us promptly of any changes to your personal circumstances.

This Privacy Policy supplements, but does not supersede, any data protection notice that has previously been provided to you.
